certapro.com 2018-09-03

# CertaPro Privacy Policy - Privacy Information - CertaPro Painters ®

Certa ProPainters, Ltd. (“CertaPro®” or “we”, “us” or “our”) respects the privacy needs of users of its website (the “Website”). This Privacy Policy describes the information practices of CertaPro®, including the information that CertaPro® collects about you, how that information is used and shared, and your choices regarding collection and use of that information.

Please review this Privacy Policy carefully before use of the Website. Your use of the Website will be deemed to be your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and the manner in which we collect, use, disclose and otherwise manage your information.

## Types of Information We Collect

We collect several types of information from and about users of the Website.

 **Information We Collect Directly From You.** If you request information about CertaPro® services, enter sweepstakes or promotions, request an estimate, register for mailing lists, request information about CertaPro® franchise opportunities, submit comments or otherwise interact with the Website, we collect the information that you manually provide. This information may include personal information such as your name, email address, postal address and telephone number, as well as details about the property you wish to have painted. At the time we collect this information, we may ask your permission to send you future marketing information.

 **Information We Collect Automatically.** CertaPro® may collect certain information automatically, including your IP address, your operating system, your location, the types of Internet browsers and devices you use and information about the way you use the Website. This information may be collected by cookies, web beacons and other technologies.

## Use of Your Information by CertaPro®

We use the information that is collected from your use of the Website to provide the information and/or services that you request. In order to do so, we may need to share your information with independently owned and operated CertaPro® franchisees and other third parties.

We may also use the information you provide us to contact you from time to time to provide you with important information, customer support, required notices and marketing promotions and offers.

We may also use the information you provide us or that is that is collected from your use of the Website to monitor or improve the use of the Website, and for internal business analysis or other business purposes.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may share your information with affiliates, franchisees and agents of CertaPro® for various purposes, including scheduling an estimate, performing services or providing customer service.

We may disclose your information as required or permitted by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process. We may also disclose your information when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

We may share aggregated, anonymized data with third parties for marketing, research, analytics and other business purposes.

## Data Security

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We incorporate reasonable safeguards to protect the information that we process and maintain. Please be aware that although we endeavor to provide reasonable security for information that we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches. Our security policies and procedures are reviewed periodically and revised as appropriate.

The website is not intended for use by children, and CertaPro® does not knowingly collect personal information from or market to children.

Information collected by CertaPro® may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers and/or servers located outside of your state, province, territory or country. By visiting the website, you consent to the transfer and storage of information by CertaPro® as we deem appropriate.

## Third Party Sites

The website may contain links to other websites or resources. These links are for your convenience only and are not under our control and are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of each such website to determine how your information will be used.

## Choices About How We Collect and Use Your Information

 **Tracking Technologies.** We use “cookies” on the Website, which are small text files that are stored on a user’s computer and allow websites to remember information about users. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, and you have the choice to set your browser to accept or reject cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features and services made available through the Website.

 **Electronic Marketing Communications.** If we sent you a promotional email, you can follow the unsubscribe link in the footer of the email or email us at Unsubscribe@CertaPro.com with “Unsubscribe” in the subject line.

 **Direct Mail Communications.** If you do not want us to send you any promotional offers through direct mail, you can email us at customersforlife@certapro.com with “Do Not Mail” in the subject line.

## Notice to California Consumers

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, consumers residing in California may request from us once a year, free of charge, certain information about the disclosure of personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to customersforlife@certapro.com .

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy to accommodate new technologies, industry practices, regulatory requirements or for other purposes. You are advised to check this privacy policy regularly, as continued use is deemed to be approval of and consent to all such changes.

## Comments and Questions

If you have a comment or question about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at customersforlife@certapro.com.

Last Modified: April 11, 2017
